questions = [
    {
      "category": "Politics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "There was a satirical candidate named 'Deez Nuts'; running in the 2016 US presidential elections.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The color orange is named after the fruit.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Comics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "The 'Pepe' meme originated from a comic drawn by Matt Furie called 'Boy's Club'?",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Adolf Hitler was accepted into the Vienna Academy of Fine Arts.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "The USS Missouri (BB-63) last served in the Korean War.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Politics",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Nazi Germany surrendered on Harry Truman's birthday while he was president.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Watch_Dogs 2 is a prequel.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Animals",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "You can tell the age of a ladybird by counting the spots on his back.",
      "correct_answer": "False",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "True"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Sports",
      "type": "boolean",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "ATP tennis hosted several tournaments on carpet court before being replaced to reduce injuries.",
      "correct_answer": "True",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "False"
      ]
    }
]
